# Harshal Khode

### Mobile Application Developer

An individual with a keen interest in Software programs, possessing good interpersonal and analytical skills, wish to work in a hard and challenging environment that will serve me generous opportunities for learning. 3 Years of experience in software field, 2 Year experience in Flutter mobile application development with knowledge of core php, core java, MySQL, Firebase. During job, Involved in planning, frontend designing, database structure designing, and Mobile Application Development.

### **Employment History**

# Mobile Application Developer(Flutter) At Disha Innovations, Khargone

March, 2020 - Present

- Working as a Flutter Mobile Application Developer.
- Part of Project planning, front-end designing, database structure designing.
- Developed multiple flutter application for e-commerce platforms, corporate management, communities.

#### Junior Developer, Teacher At Expert Technology, Khargone

March, 2019 - March, 2020

- Worked on core php, html, Android(core java), wordpress.
- Teaching C, C++ programming languages.

#### **Education**

# Shree Ji Institute Of Technology And Management(RGPV), Khargone

August, 2013 - Jun, 2017

Graduated with 7.56 CGPA

## **Work Experience**

- Badabhalu (Flutter): Ecom-Application for Customer, Seller, Delivery partner,
   Available on Play Store & App Sore.
- Astro balaji (Flutter App): Astrologer App, Available on Play Store.
- Plum (Flutter): Multi Vendor ecommerce app
- Kiraye pay (Flutter): Provider, Operator and Customer App for booking of construction equipments.
- Parichayika(Android): Community App, Available on Play Store.
- Other Flutter Apps(MRIE, ShareMark, Carpenter) for Corporate Specific Operations.

### **Details**

Sita Vihar Colony Khargone Khargone, 451001 India +91 8839138577 mrhk1703@gmail.com

### Skills

Flutter

Firebase

MySql

Github

Core Java

Core PHP

### Language

English Hindi